Fausold, Martin; Papers ua902.078
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General Research and Subject Files, 1919-2008; Undated; 2; 4 cubic ft. 1 Digital Files
  - Article about Judith Moyers Resignation from SUNY Board of Trustees, 1989 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - "Autopsy on Old Westbury" Article, 1971 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees, 1977 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Book Ideas About SUNY System, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Bound Gould Research Materials, Undated (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Boyer Biography and Notes, 1996 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Boyer's Five Year Plan Newsweek Article, 1973 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Bundy Aid and Budget, 1987 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Button Written Articles, 1956; Undated (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Central Administration SUNY State-Wide Records Inventory, Undated (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education Quote, 1988 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Columbia University: About Columbia, 2005 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Comment: History of SUNY by Harold Wechster, Undated (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Conference Session 1, Const. Foundations, 1988 April 15 (Cassette 19-20)
  - Copies of Governor Thomas Dewey's Correspondence, 1946 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Cornell Special Exhibitions and Fausold Notes, 1988 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence and Status Updates about Project, 1998; 2000; 2002 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Andersen, David, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Anslow, William, 1988 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Burke, Joseph, 1988-1990 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Burton, John, 1989 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Carlino, Joseph, 1989 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Colohan, Thomas and Bruce Leslie, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Frisch, Michael, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, General, 1988-1992 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, General, 2002-2003 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Gould, Samuel and Christopher, 1987-2003; Undated (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Harter, Carol, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Hatton, Arthur, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Johnstone, D. Bruce, 1989 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, Kalas, John, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, Leslie, Bruce, 1988-1989; 1998; 2002 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, Leslie, Bruce and Wayne Mahood, 2004 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, Mahood, Wayne, 2002-2003 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, Mahood, Wayne and Mitchell Robinson, 1987 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, Moore, Maurice, 1991 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, Park, Larry, 1988 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, Pritts, William E., 2003 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, Request for Information about Gould Era, 2005-2008 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, Skemer, Don, 1988 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, SUNY Central, 1988 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, SUNY History Project, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, Waxman, Irving, 1989 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, Wechsler, Harold, 1988 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, Wharton, Clifton R., 1988; 1997; Undated (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, Williams, Geoffrey, 2002-2005 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - The Culture of Professionalism by Burton Bledstein, Undated (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Decision-Making for Higher Education in New York State by Freda Martens, 1966 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - The Development of Policy for the Centralized Administration of the Overseas Academic Programs of SUNY by Larrie John Dean, 1974 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Dissertations to be Ordered for Research, 2003 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - A Draft History of the State University of New York, 1988; 4.45 MB (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 53-54)
  - Draft History of SUNY Geneseo, The Expansion Years, 2005 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - An Early View of the Land-Grant Colleges and Penn State Fact Sheet, 1967; 2005 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Empire State College News, US News Interview with Ernest Boyer and Personal Notes, 1972; 1985-1986 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - The Executive Budget in New York State, 1981 (Box 1 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 58-59)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes and Member List, 1988-1990 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Fausold Biography and Miscellaneous Notes, Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Fausold Campaign for Supervisor, 1955 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Fausold Family Correspondence, 2005 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - File on the Research Foundation of Statue University of New York, 1984; 1988; Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Final Report of the Commission, 1976 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Finding Aides and Dissertations to be Ordered, 2002; 2004; Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Finding Aides for Archival Collections at SUNY Stonybrook, 2002 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Freda Martens, 1961-1967; 1979-1989 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 9-10)
  - Freda Martens Publish Papers, 1961-1966; Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 11-13)
  - Functions of a Modern University, Proceedings of the First Symposium Sponsored by SUNY, 1950 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Funding SUNY: The Historic Interaction of Budgets and Politics by Martin Fausold, 1999; Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - "The Geneseo Emeritus" Newsletter, 1999 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - GI Bill Book Excerpts, 1996; 1997 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Gould, Samuel, Miscellaneous Research and Notes, 1966-1968; 2002-2008; Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Gould Publications List, Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Gould Red Books, 1966-1970 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Government and Higher Schools in New York State by Joseph Kershaw, 1979 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Government Policy and Higher Education by Frank Abbott, 1958 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 22-23)
  - Governor Rockefeller in New York by James Underwood and William Daniels, 1982 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Graduated Education in New York State, an Historical Perspective by Robert Spencer and Notes, 1985 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - The Growth of Higher Education in New York State from Colonial Days to the Present by Freda Martens, 1960 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - The Harvests of Knowledge by Theodore Blegen, 1957 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Higher Education Handwritten Notes, Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Historians, Political Scientists, and Politicians Brought to SUNY Geneseo by Fausold in 1960s-1980s, Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Histories of SUNY Cortland, 1989; Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - History of Fredonia and President Oscar Lanford, 1997; 2001 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - History of Higher Education Annual Symposium, 2000 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - History of Higher Education Newsletter and Correspondence with Edwin Duryea, 1987; 1989 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - History of State University of New York Project Conference (Aborted), 1988 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - History of State University of New York Project Mission, Goals, and Announcements, Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - History of SUNY Chronology by Fausold, Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - History of SUNY Stony Brook by John Marburger III, 1988 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - History, State University of New York Prospectus, 1997 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - The Inauguration of Christopher C. Dahl Program, 1996 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Journal of American History Articles, 1987 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Landmarks of Thompkins County, NY, Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - The Legislature and Higher Education in New York State, 1964 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - List of New York Governors, Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - "The Making of SUNY" Conference Planning, 2002 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Memories of James J. Warren, Undated (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Memories of Thomas E. Dewey, ca. 1992 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Monthly Award Summary for Oral History Project, 2002 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Moore v. Board of Regents Case Summary, 1978 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Nelson Rockefeller and the Politics of Higher Education in New York State by Judith Glazer, 1986 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - New Models of Excellence by Nancy Cooper Diamond, 2000 (Box 2 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - New York Establishes a State University by Oliver Carmichael Jr., 1955 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
  - New York-Pennsylvania Higher Education Project, 1986-1988 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - New York State Archives Report, 1981-1988 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - New York State Higher Education Policy System 1940-1980 by Karen Noonan, 1987 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 5-6)
  - New York Times Articles about SUNY, Notes, and Indexes, 1970-1971; 1975-1977; Undated (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - The New York Times Index, 1946 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - News Articles and Statements Published about or by Ernest Boyer, 1970-1978; 1995; Undated (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Newsday Notes by Robert Keeler and Notes Given to Fausold because of his Help, 1992; 2005 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 10-11)
  - One Shining Moment Drafts and Notes on the Founding of SUNY, Undated (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - The Opponents of Public Education: New York State, 1870-1880 by Gerard Postiglione, 1982 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Oral History of Martin Fausold, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Oral History Revelations of Early SUNY, Undated (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Origins and Development, State University of New York by R. W. Spencer, 1977 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 16-17)
  - Origins and Development, State University of New York by R. W. Spencer, Appendices, 1977 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Oral History Project Research Discussion Materials, 2002 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - An Overview of the The State University of New York, a series carried by The New York Times, 1981 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Papers by and about Boyer and Information about The Boyer Center, 1970-1972; 1998-2007; Undated (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Past As Prologue, SUNY First Quarter Century, Undated (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - The People's College Movement in New York State by Walter Rogers, 1945 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Perspectives on Higher Education edited by Burton Clark, 1980 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - The Politics of Architecture: A Perspective on Nelson Rockefeller, Undated (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - The Present State of Higher Education in New York State by Freda Martens, Undated (Oversized 1)
  - Press, 1970-1976 (Flat-file 1-2)
  - Press, 1989-2008 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Proposal for SUNY 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Public History of the State University of New York Strategy Session, 1988 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - The Qualified Student by Harold Wechsler, Undated (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - The Quiet Titan of Higher Education Prospectus, Undated (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Reaching the Second Plateau by Samuel Gould, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Register of the Fausold Family Papers, 2005 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Report of the Temporary Commission on the Need for a State University, 1948 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - A Report on Research Potentials and Problems in the State University of New York, 1957 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Research Foundation Application and Acceptance Letter, 1988 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Research Foundation Expenses and Correspondence, 1984; 1987-1989 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Research Foundation Founding Possibilities, 1989 (Box 3 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Research Funding Possibilities, 1988 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Research Materials Oral SUNY History Project, 2002 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 2-3)
  - Rochester Democrat and Chronicle Articles about SUNY, Undated (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center, 2004; 2005 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller in Retrospect: The Governor's New York Legacy edited by Gerald Benjamin and T. Norman Hurd, 1984 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller of New York, Executive Power in the Statehouse by Robert Connery and Gerald Benjamin, 1979 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Short Biography about Alton Marshall, 1968-1970 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Sixty-Four Campuses published by Office of University Affairs and Development, 1985 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - The State Colleges and Universities by Richard Scher, 1972 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - The State Colleges and Universities by Richard Scher, 1972 (Oversized 1)
  - The State University of New York and Community Colleges from 1948-1973 by Pauline Fitzgerald, 1974 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - State University of New York Board of Trustees Annual Report and Personal Notes, 1951; Undated (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - State University of New York Directory, 1965; 1975; 1984; 1994 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - State University of New York: Fulfilling The Promise by Glenn DuBois, 1999 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - State University of New York Oral History Project Annotated Bibliography, Undated (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - State University of New York, The Master Plan, 1960 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - State University of New York Red Book, Undated (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - SUNY Albany Graduate Public History Program, Undated (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - SUNY and the Regents Outline, 1989 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - "The SUNY Archives and Their Analyses" Conference, 1987 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - SUNY Archives Meeting in Buffalo, 1988 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - SUNY Art American Artist Article, 1975 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - SUNY Articles, 2003; Undated (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - SUNY Bibliography, Undated (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - SUNY Binghamton Article, 2004 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - SUNY Budget, Undated (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - SUNY Budget Process, 1962-1989 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - SUNY Buffalo Article, Undated (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - SUNY Buffalo Articles, 1970 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - SUNY Central Administration Functional Organization Chart, 1988 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - SUNY Central Office Structure and Directories, 1949-1986 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - SUNY, CUNY, and the Independent Colleges by Donald Barr, 1985 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - SUNY Distinguished Professor Gerald Benjamin, 2002 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - SUNY Geneseo Listings in National Publications, 1989; 1996; Undated (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - "A SUNY Grad is One in a Million", 1985 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - SUNY History Conference, 2008 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - SUNY New Paltz Articles, 1981; 1993; 1995 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - "SUNY Past as Prologue: Six Articles", 1992 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - SUNY Per Capita Expenditure in NY, 1994-1995 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - SUNY Sponsored Program Activity Report, 1989 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - The University of New York and Its French Inspiration by Charles Beatty Alexander, 1919 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Thomas E. Dewey and His Times by Richard Norton Smith, 1982 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - The Transformation of the City University of New York, 1945-1970 by Sheila Gordon, 1975 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Visiting Professorships GRI Program, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Wharton File, 1981-1982; 2003 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Wharton Publications, 1993; 2003 (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Win or Lose-How History's Great Political Leaders Played The Game by Dick Morris and Personal Pictures, Undated (Box 4 (2-General Research and Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Where Are We Going? Conference, ca. May 16 (Cassette 16-18)
- FASUNY, 1948-1969; Undated; 3; 2 cubic ft.
  Series 3 consists of Fausold's records during his time as Vice President and President of the Faculty Association of the State University of New York (FASUNY). FASUNY's purpose was to promote unity within the SUNY System faculty. The organization was concerned with not only improving the general welfare of SUNY faculty, but with improving education opportunities in the State of New York as well. FASUNY informed members of its efforts through its newsletter. This series contains copies of the Association's newsletters from 1957-1968 as well as mailing lists. FASUNY hosted a biennial conference where members of the Association met to discuss problems of public higher education and conduct Association related business. This series also includes FASUNY meeting minutes, membership information and Fausold's 1960s professional correspondence. Fausold also kept records of the SUNY budget, payroll, and salary reports.
  It should be noted that there are three folders within this series that are labeled as a "Chronological File." While not descriptive, this was Fausold's original title and the archivist preserved it.
  - Association of New York State Teachers College Faculties, 1948-1958 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 1)
  - Association of New York State Teachers College Faculties Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1956-1959 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 2)
  - Association of New York State Teachers College Faculties Constitution, Undated (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 3)
  - Biennial Conference, 1960 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 4)
  - Biennial Conference, 1962 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 5)
  - Biennial Conference, 1964 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 6)
  - Biennial Conference, 1966 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 7)
  - Biennial Conference Controversy, 1960-1964 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 8)
  - Biennial Conference Program Speakers Correspondence, 1964 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 9-10)
  - Chronological File, 1963-1965 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 11)
  - Chronological File, 1966 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 12)
  - Chronological File, 1967 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 13)
  - Community College Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Adams-Bridges, 1964-1968 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 15)